











Enthusiastic web developer who's all about creating products that people genuinely enjoy. I care about making customers happy and prioritize testing, accessibility, teamwork, and writing quality code.

My skill set includes **JavaScript, React, Node.js, and MongoDB.** Excited about bringing this passion and expertise to a fun and dynamic work environment that values innovation in web development.

# SKILLS

#### Front-end









## Back-end









#### Others















#### LANGUAGES

**Spanish** - Native

English - C1

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **Full-Stack Developer**



Feb 2024 - Presente

Nextpyme Servicios Informáticos

Working with JavaScript, Node.js, Laravel, PHP, SQL, HTML, Bootstrap, and Vue.js, I work alongside the CEO to transform client needs into practical web solutions.Leveraging my skills in JavaScript, Node.js, Laravel, PHP, SQL, HTML, Bootstrap, and Vue.js, I work alongside the CEO to transform client needs into practical web solutions.

### **Full-Stack Developer**



Jul 2023 - Dic 2023

Oxygen Workspace

I am involved in the complete development process of a hotel reservation management application using the **MERN** (MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, Node.js) technical stack.

Projects linked to this experience:

Travl Hotel Dashboard: www.tinyurl.com/mirhotdash
Hotel Miranda: www.tinyurl.com/mirhote
Oxygen Free Stock Photos: www.tinyurl.com/picgen

## ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

## **Bootcamp Full Stack**

REBOUT ACADEMY

2021 - 2022

Mastered **JavaScript, Nuxt.js, MongoDB, Express.js, Vue.js**, and **Node.js** through an immersive web dev bootcamp. Now, I craft top-notch applications on both the client and server sides. Acquired hands-on expertise and in-depth knowledge during dynamic projects and comprehensive training.







